Guide to the Rabinowitz, Boudin, Standard, Krinsky and Lieberman Legal Files TAM.287
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: General Legal Work and Client Files, 1915-1992
  - ACA: Mackay Radio and Telegraph Company, Inc. - FCC Docket # 9093, 1945-1950 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - ACA: Mackay Radio and Telegraph Company, Inc. - Station Closures, 1950 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - ACA: Marine Department, 1945-1948 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - ACA: Merger Issues, 1948, 1955-1963 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - ACA: Merger Proceedings, 1937-1940 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - ACA: Merger Proceedings - Postal Telegraph and Cable Corp., 1939 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - ACA: Merger Proceedings - Telegraph Employees under the Fair Labor Standards Act, 1940 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - ACA: National Association of Broadcast Employees & Technicians (NABET) - Dispute over Representation at ABC and NBC, 1967 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - ACA: NABET - Dispute over Representation at ABC and NBC, By-Laws and Agreements, 1964-1967 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - ACA: NABET - Dispute over Representation at ABC and NBC, Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - ACA: NABET - Dispute over Representation at ABC and NBC, Legal Memos and Notes, 1967 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - ACA: NCR Corporation - NLRB Case 2-RC-17169, 1976-1978 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - ACA: National Food Service, Inc. - Arbitration, 1954-1955 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - ACA: New Broadcasting Company - ACA v. New Broadcasting Co., Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - ACA: New Broadcasting Company - Arbitrations, 1951-1956, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - ACA: New Broadcasting Company - Arbitration - Kantrowitz, Arthur Discharge (WLIB), 1948-1953 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - ACA: New Broadcasting Company - Contract Negotiations / Arrests for Handbill Distribution, 1950-1951 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - ACA: New Broadcasting Company - NLRB Case 2-CA-1429 (WLIB), 1950 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - ACA: New Broadcasting Company - NLRB Case 2-CA-1703 (WLIB), 1950-1951 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - ACA: New Broadcasting Company - New Broadcasting Co. v. William Bender and ACA, 1970-1973 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - ACA: New England Telephone, 1966 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - ACA: New York Telephone Company and Technical Electronics and Communications Union (TECU), 1967 (Box 73, Folder 23)
  - ACA: Office Space Leases, 1943-1945, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - ACA: Park Row Lease Termination - Security Issues, 1973 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - ACA: Pension Plan, 1966, 1973-1974 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - ACA: Pension Trust Agreement, 1961, 1974-1982 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - ACA: Postal Telegraph and American Radio Telegraphists' Assn. (ARTA) / NLRB, 1937-1938 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - ACA: Postal Telegraph and ARTA / NLRB, 1937-1939 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - ACA: Press Wireless, Inc. - Insolvency, 1947 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - ACA: Press Wireless, Inc. - Transfer of Control to International Telephone and Telegraph (IT&T), 1964 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - ACA: Press Wireless, Inc. - Transfer of Control to IT&T, 1964-1966 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - ACA: Propriety of Screening Telegraph Messages, 1955 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - ACA: Public Coast Radiotelegraphic Services (FCC), 1978 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - ACA v. City of New York…and RCA Communications, 1962-1963 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - ACA v. RCA Communications, Equitable Life Insurance Society and Morgan Guaranty Trust (RCA Employee's Retirement Plan), 1964-1972 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - ACA v. RCA, Formal (I), 1967 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - ACA v. RCA, Formal (II), 1967 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - ACA v. RCA, Formal (I), 1968 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - ACA v. RCA, Formal (II), 1968 (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - ACA v. RCA, Formal, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - ACA v. RCA, Formal, 1970 (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - Application for Assignment of Radio Station Licenses, 1966-1967 (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - Application to Close Station KSE (Torrance CA), 1964 (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - Arbitration - Berger, Paul and Kaufman, Michael, 1968 (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - Arbitration - Bodner, Richard S., 1959-1960 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - Arbitration - Grumman, Frank; Stallone, Louis; Chew, Willis, 1957-1958 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - Arbitration - Grumman, Stallone and Chew, Correspondence, 1956-1958 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - Arbitration - Grumman, Stallone and Chew, Exhibits, 1947-1957 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - Arbitration - Grumman, Stallone and Chew, Transcripts, Feb 17, 1958 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - Arbitration - Grumman, Stallone and Chew, Transcripts, Feb 18, 1958 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - Arbitration - Grumman, Stallone and Chew, Transcripts, Mar 28, 1958 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - Arbitration - Minimum Rates of Pay, 1966-1967 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - Arbitration - Painting Sub-Contract, 1960-1961 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - Arbitration - Testa, Salvatore A. and Trautman, Howard V., 1957-1958 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - Arbitration - Testa and Trautman, Congressional Committee Hearings, 1957 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - Arbitration - Testa and Trautman, Exhibits (I), 1951-1957 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - Arbitration - Testa and Trautman, Exhibits (II), 1951-1957 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - Arbitration - Testa and Trautman, Newspaper Clippings, 1957 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - Arbitration - Testa and Trautman, Transcript (I), Oct 15, 1957 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - Arbitration - Testa and Trautman, Transcript (II), Oct 15, 1957 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - Arbitration - Testa and Trautman, Transcript (A.M.), Oct 16, 1957 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - Arbitration - Testa and Trautman, Transcript (P.M.), Oct 16, 1957 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - Arbitration - Testa and Trautman, Transcript (I), Oct 17, 1957 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - Arbitration - Testa and Trautman, Transcript (II), Oct 17, 1957 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - Arbitration - Willis, John and Ingoglia, Vincent, 1961-1962 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - Arbitration - Various, 1959-1978 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - Contract Negotiations, 1967-1968 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - FCC Docket # 19544, 1976-1978 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - Hawaiian Stations, 1950-1953, 1967-1968 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - Hawaiian Stations, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - Kelly, Robert P. et al. v. Martin P. Catherwood, 1968-1970 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - Kelly v. Catherwood, 1968-1972 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - Kelly, Robert P., Unemployment Insurance Claims, 1967-1969 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - Local 10 By-Laws, 1967 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - Local 10 Members Accused of Criminal Trespass, 1967-1968 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - Message Issues, 1960-1968 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - Personnel Security Questionnaire, 1954 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - Pregnancy, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - Program Relay Service Technicians, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - RCA v. ACA, Local 10 and Vincent Attardi, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - RCA v. Selly et al.(Alleged Picket Intimidation, Disruption and Violence), 1967 (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - RCA v. Selly et al., 1967-1968 (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - RCA Global Application to Close Lodi California Operating Center (FCC), 1978 (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - RCA Global Communications, Inc. v. ACA and Local 10(Picketing, Intimidation, Violence), 1978 (Box 76, Folder 20)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - Reducing Office Hours in San Francisco, 1951 (Box 76, Folder 21)
  - ACA: RCA Communications - West Coast Union Shop, 1953 (Box 76, Folder 22)
  - ACA: Seaboard Radio Broadcasting Corporation, 1947-1957 (Box 76, Folder 23)
  - ACA: Selly, Joseph P. v. Commercial Telegraphers' Union, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 24)
  - ACA: Severance Pay, 1949 (Box 76, Folder 25)
  - ACA: Smythe, Dallas, 1964-1965 (Box 76, Folder 26)
  - ACA: Speed of Service Standards, 1947-1954 (Box 76, Folder 27)
  - ACA: Speed of Service Standards - FCC Docket # 12495, 1958 (Box 76, Folder 28)
  - ACA: Stafford Manuscript (Michigan Bell Telephone Co.) 1 of 3, 1942-1945 (Box 76, Folder 29)
  - ACA: Stafford Manuscript (Michigan Bell Telephone Co.) 2 of 3, 1942-1945 (Box 76, Folder 30)
  - ACA: Stafford Manuscript (Michigan Bell Telephone Co.) 3 of 3, 1942-1945 (Box 76, Folder 31)
  - ACA: State Farm Mutual Automobile Insurance Company - Various Cases, 1966-1973 (Box 76, Folder 32)
  - ACA: State Farm Mutual Automobile Insurance Company - Various Cases, 1967-1971 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - ACA: State Farm Mutual Automobile Insurance Company - Various Cases, 1970-1976 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - ACA: Station WABF (Metropolitan Broadcasting Corp.), 1947-1952 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - ACA: Station WBL, Buffalo NY, 1951 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - ACA: Station WFIL, 1941-1949 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - ACA: Station WGBB, 1950-1951 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - ACA: Station WHOM (Atlantic Broadcasting Company), 1946-1953 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - ACA: Station WIBG, 1951 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - ACA: Station WLIB (I), 1948-1959 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - ACA: Station WLIB (II), 1948-1959 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - ACA: Station WMCA, 1949, 1951 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - ACA: Station WMGM, 1949-1952 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - ACA: Station WNEW (I), 1943-1951 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - ACA: Station WNEW (II), 1943-1951 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - ACA: Station WNYC, 1947, Undated (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - ACA: Station WOV (Wodaam Corporation) (I), 1946-1950 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - ACA: Station WOV (Wodaam Corporation (II), 1946-1950 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - ACA: Station WPEN, 1952 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - ACA: Station WQQW, 1949 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - ACA: Strike - Arrests, 1948 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.21) - General (including War Labor Board Telephone Cases), 1943-1944 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.21) - General (including War Labor Board Telephone Cases), 1945 (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.21) - General, 1946-1947 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.21) - General, Correspondence, 1944-1948 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.21) - Organizational Notes, 1944 (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.22) - Contracts, 1944 (Box 77, Folder 26)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.23111) - Federation of Long Lines Telephone Workers (FLLTW) Local Affiliation, Detroit Traffic, 1936-1944 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2312) - NLRB Petitions (Washington, No. California, Oregon), 1944-1947 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2313) - Southern Bell Telephone Company, 1943-1944 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2314) - Michigan Bell Telephone Company, 1944-1945 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2315) - Southern California Telephone Company, 1944-1945, 1947 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2316) - West Coast Telephone Company, 1945 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2321) - AT&T, Detroit Traffic Department, 1944 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2322) - Michigan Bell - Bulletins, Evidence and Various Division-Related Materials (I), 1934-1945 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2322) - Michigan Bell - Bulletins, Evidence and Various Division-Related Materials (II), 1934-1945 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2322) - Michigan Bell - Contracts, By-Laws, 1928-1943 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2322) - Michigan Bell - Correspondence, 1944-1946 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2322) - Michigan Bell - Leaflets, 1943-1946 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2322) - Michigan Bell - Legal File, 1944 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2323) - Southern California Telephone Company, 1944-1947 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2324) - Pacific Telephone and Telegraph Company (PT&T), 1945-1947 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2411) - Contract Negotiations and War Labor Board - PT&T Local 101, Briefs and Memos, 1943-1944 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2411) - Contract Negotiations and War Labor Board - PT&T Local 101, Correspondence, 1943-1944 (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2411) - Contract Negotiations and War Labor Board - PT&T Local 101, Decision of WLB Case 918, 1943 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2411) - Contract Negotiations and War Labor Board - PT&T Local 101, Drafts and Exhibits, 1941-1943 (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2411) - Contract Negotiations and War Labor Board - PT&T Local 101, Negotiations, Bulletins and Contracts, 1944-1946 (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2411) - Contract Negotiations and War Labor Board - PT&T Local 101, Proposals and Contract, 1947 (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2411) - Contract Negotiations and War Labor Board - PT&T Local 101, Transcript of Hearing, WLB Case 10-12040, 1944 (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2411) - Contract Negotiations and War Labor Board - PT&T Local 101, Wage Stabilization Report, 1941-1943 (Box 78, Folder 22)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2412) - Contract Negotiation, PT&T Local 120, 1944, 1947 (Box 78, Folder 23)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.242) - Contract Negotiations and War Labor Board - Northwestern Telephone Company, Briefs, 1943 (Box 78, Folder 24)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.242) - Contract Negotiations and War Labor Board - Northwestern Telephone Company, Contract, 1943 (Box 78, Folder 25)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.242) - Contract Negotiations and War Labor Board - Northwestern Telephone Company, Correspondence, 1943-1944 (Box 78, Folder 26)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.242) - Contract Negotiations and War Labor Board - Northwestern Telephone Company, Drafts and Legal File, 1943 (Box 78, Folder 27)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.281) - Federation of Long Lines Telephone Workers (FLLTW) Constitution, Contract, 1942 (Box 78, Folder 28)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.282) - Federation Voice and UTO News, 1943 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.283) - Order of Repeatermen and Toll Testboardmen (ORTT), 1941-1942 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.284) - Organization Memos, 1943-1945 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.285) - Washington Federation of Telephone Workers, 1943-1944 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.288) - National Federation of Telephone Workers (NFTW) (I), 1939-1947 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.288) - National Federation of Telephone Workers (NFTW) (II), 1939-1947 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.289) - Strike (Nov 1944 and Oct 1945), 1944-1945 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2810) - Individual Bargaining Sec. 9, 1944 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2311) - TWX and WU Merger, 1945 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2812) - Western Electric, 1945 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2813) - Western Electric Employees Assn. and United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers (UERMWA), 1945 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2815) - Telephone Traffic Employees' Organization (TTEO), San Francisco, 1945-1946 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2816) - National Federation of Telephone Workers (NFTW) Strike, 1946 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2817) - War Labor Board Papers re New York State Units, 1942-1943 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2818) - Telephone Workers Industrial Union, 1945-1946 (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2819) - AT&T Stockholders Meeting and Proxy, 1946 (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2820) - United Brotherhood of Telephone Workers (UBTW), Los Angeles, 1946 (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2821) - Telephone Wage Data, 1945-1946 (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2822) - Communication Workers of America (CWA) Proposed Constitution and CWA News, 1946-1947 (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2823) - Association of Communications Equipment Workers (ACEW), 1947 (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2824) - Bell Laboratory, New York, 1947 (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2825) - National Federation of Telephone Workers (NFTW) Strike, 1947 (Box 79, Folder 22)
  - ACA: Telephone(1.2826) - Telephone Workers Organizing Committee, 1947 (Box 79, Folder 23)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2827) - Telephone Traffic Employees Association (TTEO) Local 120 By-Laws, 1947 (Box 79, Folder 24)
  - ACA: Telephone (1.2828) - United Brotherhood of Telephone Workers (NBTW), San Francisco, 1947 (Box 79, Folder 25)
  - ACA: Teleregister Corporation, 1946-1949 (Box 79, Folder 26)
  - ACA: TRT Telecommunications, 1978 (Box 79, Folder 27)
  - ACA: Unemployment Insurance Appeal - Bucich, Matteo, 1966 (Box 79, Folder 28)
  - ACA: Unemployment Insurance Matters, 1949-1956 (Box 79, Folder 29)
  - ACA: Unemployment Insurance Matters - DeQuattro, George, 1949-1950 (Box 79, Folder 30)
  - ACA: United Broadcasting Company - Election, 1961 (Box 79, Folder 31)
  - ACA: Various Drafts, Notes, Publications and Documents, 1960-1977, Undated (Box 79, Folder 32)
  - ACA: Wage Control Information, 1971-1972, Undated (Box 79, Folder 33)
  - ACA: Western Union - Action to Stay Arbitration, NY Supreme Court (I), 1946-1951 (Box 79, Folder 34)
  - ACA: Western Union - Action to Stay Arbitration, NY Supreme Court (II), 1946-1951 (Box 79, Folder 35)
  - ACA: Western Union - ACA v. American Cable & Radio Corp. and Western Union Telegraph Company, 1959 (Box 79, Folder 36)
  - ACA: Western Union - ACA and Western Union (Cable Division) Case #111-14542-D, 1943-1945 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - ACA: Western Union - ACA v. City of New York and Western Union, 1962-1963 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - ACA: Western Union - ACA v. City of New York and Western Union, Formal, 1962-1963 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - ACA: Western Union - Applications to Close Branch Offices and Reduce Hours, 1958-1959 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - ACA: Western Union - Arbitration, 1959 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - ACA: Western Union - Arbitration - Bott, Thomas, 1951 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - ACA: Western Union - Arbitration - Cuciti, Salvatore and Melvey, Joseph, 1957-1958 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - ACA: Western Union - Arbitration - Goding, Margaret, 1956-1957 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - ACA: Western Union - Arbitration - Lagos, Frank and Lillian; Bollinger, Ruth, 1956-1957 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - ACA: Western Union - Arbitration - Lagos, Frank and Lillian; Bollinger, Ruth - Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - ACA: Western Union - Arbitration - Laudadio, Emanuel, 1953-1954 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - ACA: Western Union - Arbitration - Levitt, Max; Browne, O.H. and Hammond, M., 1953 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - ACA: Western Union - Arbitration - November, Maurice, 1953-1954 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - ACA: Western Union - Arbitration re Teleprinters' Night Tour, 1952-1953 (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - ACA: Western Union - Arbitration Transcripts (I), 1959 (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - ACA: Western Union - Arbitration Transcripts (II), 1959 (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - ACA: Western Union - Case # 111-14542-D (WLB), Negotiations, 1943-1945 (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - ACA: Western Union - Case # 111-14542-D (WLB), Related Material, 1942-1945 (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - ACA: Western Union - Commercial Telegraphers' Union Election, 1962 (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - ACA: Western Union - Complaint re Hourly Rate Reduction (Starace, Louis et al.) (I), 1946-1948 (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - ACA: Western Union - Complaint re Hourly Rate Reduction (Starace, Louis et al.) (II), 1946-1948 (Box 80, Folder 21)
  - ACA: Western Union - Contract Negotiation Reopening, 1946 (Box 80, Folder 22)
  - ACA: Western Union - Contract Negotiation Reopening, 1946-1948 (Box 80, Folder 23)
  - ACA: Western Union - Contract Negotiation Reopening, Research, 1946-1947 (Box 80, Folder 24)
  - ACA: Western Union - Contracts, 1939-1943 (Box 80, Folder 25)
  - ACA: Western Union - Contracts, 1946-1954 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - ACA: Western Union - Expiration of Merger Act, 1947-1948 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - ACA: Western Union - FCC Rule Changes, 1953-1954 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - ACA: Western Union - FCC in re Western Union (International Telex), 1979-1980 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - ACA: Western Union - Local 11 Complaint re Sanitary Conditions, 1949 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - ACA: Western Union - Motion to Confirm Arbitration Award, 1948 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - ACA: Western Union - NLRB Case # 2-CB-4215, ULP Charge Filed by Plantmens' Benevolent Assn., 1965 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - ACA: Western Union - New Jersey Sick Benefit Law, 1949 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - ACA: Western Union - Newfoundland Dispute / Contract, 1948-1949 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - ACA: Western Union - Office Closing, 1966 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - ACA: Western Union - Pension and Benefit Plan, 1944-1950 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - ACA: Western Union - Pension Plan Arbitration Case # 111-3691-D, Briefs, 1943-1945 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - ACA: Western Union - Pension Plan Arbitration Case # 111-3691-D, Correspondence, 1939, 1944-1945 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - ACA: Western Union - Pension Plan Arbitration Case # 111-3691-D, Exhibits and Inserts, 1940-1946 (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - ACA: Western Union - Pension Plan Arbitration Case # 111-3691-D, Notes, 1944-1945 (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - ACA: Western Union - Pension Plan Arbitration Case # 111-3691-D, Other Companies' Plans, 1931, 1943-1944, Undated (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - ACA: Western Union - Pension Plan Arbitration Case # 111-3691-D, Related Materials, 1924, 1940-1945 (Box 81, Folder 17)
  - ACA: Western Union - Pension Plan Arbitration Case # 111-3691-D, Transcript, Mar 16, 1945 (Box 81, Folder 18)
  - ACA: Western Union - Sale of Western Union Cables, 1956 (Box 81, Folder 19)
  - ACA: Western Union - Seniority and Comparable Job Cases and Decisions under WLB Order, 1941-1945 (Box 81, Folder 20)
  - ACA: Western Union - Seniority and Comparable Job Cases and Decisions under WLB Order, 1944 (Box 81, Folder 21)
  - ACA: Western Union - Seniority and Comparable Job Cases and Decisions under WLB Order, 1945-1946 (Box 81, Folder 22)
  - ACA: Western Union - Various Agreements, Plans and Benefits Brochures, 1946-1961 (Box 81, Folder 23)
  - ACA: Western Union - Various Arbitration, Grievance and Negotiation-Related Materials (I), 1949-1966 (Box 81, Folder 24)
  - ACA: Western Union - Various Arbitration, Grievance and Negotiation-Related Materials (II), 1949-1966 (Box 81, Folder 25)
  - ACA: Western Union - Various Arbitrations, 1947-1953 (Box 81, Folder 26)
  - ACA: Western Union - Various National War Labor Board Arbitration Decisions, 1944-1945 (Box 81, Folder 27)
  - ACA: Western Union - Welfare Plan / Pension Plan, 1947-1961 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - ACA: Western Union - Western Union Cables Contract Negotiation / Canadian Employees, 1958 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - ACA: Western Union - Western Union International, FCC Docket # 6517, 1964-1965 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - ACA: Western Union - Western Union v. Joseph P. Selly(I), 1945-1947 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - ACA: Western Union - Western Union v. Selly(II), 1945-1947 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - ACA: Western Union - Western Union v. Selly(III), 1945-1946 (Box 82, Folder 6)